Envi Bagus Aditya

Product Designer

Envi is a highly skilled and motivated Product Designer who passionate about making Intuitive beautiful user-centered digital products. Have experience working with teams to analyze and create beautiful UI/UX Design based on requirements and design thinking process at varying levels of fidelity using atomic design approach. Also have some front-end coding experiences.

Experience



NATIVE PRODUCTIONS • April 2022 - Present

Freelance UI/UX Designer

Part-time Pali, Indonesia

- > Designed low-fidelities and high-fidelities for multiple projects in company correlated with Web2 and Web3.
- > Conducted UX research and interview before starting projects.
- > Coded landing page website projects using HTML, CSS, Javascript.



AIRDROP VENTURES PTE. LTD. • September 2022 - January 2023

UI/UX Designer

Full-time - Semi Remote Singapore

- > Organised and Built company complex design system for multiple products in Company.
- > Designed and Collaborated with teams in total 3 big projects correlated
- > Researched base requirements and regulation in Indonesia for building products.
- > Directed other UX Designer to speed-up and maximise workflow in Figma using Plugins, Shortcuts, Libraries, and Design System.



PT. IDOOH BERSAMA INDOESIA • June 2022 - October 2022

UI/UX Designer

Full-time - Remote 9 Jakarta, Indonesia

- > Designed and Prototyped multiple products following Tailwind UI style guides.
- > Advised in terms of design some of other products that the company have launch and currently build.
- > Directed 3 UI/UX Designers on teams.
- > Created complex design system for products and company.
- > Conducted user interview for every new projects, Created user flows, mind map, wireframes, information architecture.



MERGED, INC. . June 2022 - Nov 2022

Freelance UI/UX Designer

Part-time - Remote Ocalifornia

- > Conducted research about most popular payment banking and payment system in the United States.
- > Designed mobile low-fidelity, design system, and high-fidelity of Merged
- > Building prototypes, brand guides to be used for pitching and marketing purposes.



PT. TIGA TOKEN DIGITAL • June 2021 - September 2022

UI/UX Designer

Full-time Pali, Indonesia

- > Designed 6+ big projects related to Web3 including NFT Marketplace, Crypto Wallet Extension, Crypto Exchange, Staking, Crypto Launchpad.
- > Prepared all the designs for handover to developers as a single UX Designer in company.
- > Coded multiple landing pages for each company website products using HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- > Conducted research about Web3 and Blockchain in designer role.
- > Created graphic design for various events and social media purposes.



PT. LABELLE PELARIAN INDONESIA · Sep - 2019- Nov 2019

Product Designer

Full-time Pali, Indonesia

- > Designed and Managed versioning of Travel agent website app and Community traveling platform that focusing on women using Figma.
- > Coded website and email designs.
- > Managed website using Docker and Linux.



VENTRAPEDIA • July 2019- Dec 2020

Freelance Web Designer Part-time Pali, Indonesia

- > Designed Responsive design of Travel agent website app and Community Platform using Adobe XD.
- > Designed dashboard for managing travel platform.
- > Coded all the design using HTML, CSS, Javascript with Bootstrap and Bulma Frameworks.



PT. LUMONATA · Aug 2017 - Oct 2017

Web Designer

Internship • Bali, Indonesia

- > Focused learning Web design and Web development with teams.
- > Created some graphic designs using Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator.
- > Participated in multiple website design competitions.

Contact



envibagus@gmail.com





linkedin.com/in/envibagus



+62 878 6222 0311

Location Bali, Indonesia

Skills

Design

- > Visual Design
- > Design Thinking
- · Mobile Design · Web Design
- > UX Research
- SAAS Design
- > UX Writing
- > Design System
- > Interaction Design
- > Prototyping

Able to fully maximise features of Figma with plugins, shortcuts, hidden features, and multiple

- > Miro
- > Invision
- > Framer
- > Maze
- > Sketch
- > Linear
- > Google Workspace
- > Adobe Illustrator > Adobe Photoshop
- > Atlassian Products
- > Problem Solving
- > Project Management
- > Attention to detail
- > Adaptability
- > Public Speaking
- Development

> Version Control

- > SQL Database
- > Javascript
- > Tailwind

Certification & Awards

- Bootcamp UI/UX & Product Management
- Design Thinking Techniques for Efficiency Binar Academy • September 2022
- Output
 UX Design for Product Development Skill Academy · March 2020
- [>] 3rd Winner of Web design Paras ICT 2020 Stiki Indonesia · February 2020
- [>] 2nd Winner of National Group Web design

Universitas Bunda Mulia, Jakarta · April 2019

- [>] 3rd Winner of Web design Paras ICT 2019 Stiki Indonesia • February 2019
- Ist Winner of Web design PNBWDC Politeknik Negeri Bali • September 2018
- ³ 2nd Winner of National Web design Invention

Universitas Udayana · June 2018

Education

> ITB Stikom Bali Bachelor Degree in Information System GPA: 3.48

September 2019 - June 2023

> Harisenin.com Bootcamp Product Management and UI/UX August 2022 - January 2023

SMK TI Bali Global Vocational High school majoring in **Software Engineering**

Languages

Indonesian Native or bilingual proficiency

July 2016 - July 2019

English Professional working proficiency



Last updated on June 2023

tricks to accelerate workflow for project done. > Figjam > Zeplin

- > ProtoPie
- > Notion
- > Adobe XD
- > Microsoft 365
- **Soft Skills**
- > Leadership
- > Collaboration
- > HTML & CSS
- > Bootstrap